The Grenfell Press Archive
Rare Book and Special Collections Division, Library of Congress
- Miscellaneous Publications
  - Oates, Joyce Carol. Heat, 1989. Illustration by Robert Gober. See also: Oversize: Broadsides
    - Material relating to illustration, incl. one note from May, undated
    - Paper samples (folded sheets, blank)
  - Burroughs, William. Ghost of Chance, 1990. (92-183221) See also: Oversize: Broadsides (Box 23)
    - Correspondence, May (Whitney Museum of American Art), 1990-91 (3 items); Sue (?) (Allethaire Press), undated (1 item); Michael, [1990?] (1 item)
    - Typescripts
    - Material relating to illustration
    - Paste-ups
- Oversize. Broadsides Correspondence and Typescripts 1983-1992 (Box 24-54)
  Oversize material organized and described according to the series, folders, and boxes from which the items were removed.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Laughlin, James. The Inn at Kirchstetten, 1988?
    - Galleys, also one letter from Leslie Miller to James Laughlin, 1988
  - Grenfell Press Publications Dowell, Coleman. The Silver Swanne. 1983.
    - Galleys
  - Davenport, Guy. The Bowmen of Shu, 1983.
    - Galleys
  - Sobin, Gustav. Ten Sham Haikus. 1983.
    - Galleys
  - Lauterbach, Ann. Sacred Weather, 1984.
    - Galleys
    - Material relating to illustration
  - Galley and typescript for "Not that it could be finished" Hawkes, John. Innocence in Extremis. 1985.
    - Galleys
    - Unbound sheets (Box 25)
  - Laughlin, James. The House of Light. 1986.
    - Galleys, incl. one letter from James Laughlin, 1986 Laughlin, James. Tabellae, 1986.
    - Galleys
    - Unbound sheets
  - Sorrentino, Gilbert. A Beehive Arranged on Humane Principles. 1985. (Box 27)
    - Galleys
    - Material relating to illustration, incl. proofs
    - Unbound sheets
  - Gass, William. Culp, 1985. (Box 28)
    - Galleys
  - Duncan, Robert. A Paris Visit, 1985.
    - Galleys, incl. one letter from R.B. Kitaj [1984?] and photograph; one letter from Robert Duncan, 1984 Cole, Peter. Rjft, 1986.
    - Proofs (binding)
    - Galleys
  - Burroughs, William. The Cat Inside, 1986. (Box 29)
    - Galleys
    - Material relating to illustration, layout 5. Cloth boards
  - Unbound sheets (Box 30)
  - Unbound sheets (Box 31)
  - Unbound sheets (Box 32)
  - Mathews, Harry. Singular Pleasures, 1988. (Box 33)
    - Galleys
  - Mathews, Harry. The Way Home. 1988. (Box 33)
    - Galleys
    - Material relating to illustration
  - Morrow, Bradford. A Bestiary, 1990. (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous publications
    - Galleys
    - Miscellaneous proofs, notes
  - Plates (Snake, Hare, Mongoose, Lemming)
  - Elephant (Box 35)
  - Pig
  - Snake
  - Skunk
  - Frog
  - Frog (Box 36)
  - Scorpion
  - Starling
  - Plankton
  - Tortoise (Box 37)
  - Hare
  - Armadillo
  - Opossum
  - Owl
  - Anemone (Box 38)
  - Beetle
  - Bee
  - Trout
  - Lioness (Box 39)
  - Firefly
  - Canis
  - Earthworm (Box 40)
  - The Monkey Prince
  - Mussel
  - Beaver
  - Hummingbird
  - Unicorn
  - Bat
  - Laughlin, James. Angelica (Box 41)
    - Galleys
  - Howe, Susan. The Nonconformist's Memorial, 1992. (Box 42)
    - Galleys
    - Proofs
    - Material relating to illustration
  - Kittredge, William and Robert Helm. Lost Cowboys. (Box 43)
    - Galleys
    - Proofs
    - Unbound sheets
  - Michaux, Henri. Ideograms in China, 1984. (Box 44)
    - Galleys
  - Targ, William. Abacus Now, Targ Editions, 1984.
    - Galleys
  - The Grenfell Press 1985 Catalog. 1985.
    - Galleys
  - Fisher, M.F.K. Spirits of the Valley.
    - Galleys
  - Greene, Graham. Reflections on Travels with my Aunt, 1989.
    - Galleys
    - Material relating to frontispiece photograph, manuscript facsimile Rattray, David. Out of the Dark. 1989.
    - Galleys
  - Oates, Joyce Carol. Heat, 1989.
    - Galleys
  - Burroughs, William. Ghost of Chance. 1990. (Box 45)
    - Galleys
    - Notes relating to layout, typography, paper sample
    - Material relating to illustration, incl. one note from Condo, 1989
    - Proofs
  - Hawkes, John. Innocence in Extremis. 1985. (Box 46)
    - Unbound sheets
    - Material relating to illustration Duncan, Robert. A Paris Visit. 1985. (Box 47)
    - Material relating to illustration
    - Unbound sheets (Box 48)
  - Sorrentino, Gilbert. A Beehive Arranged on Humane Principles. 1985. (Box 49)
    - Unbound sheets
  - Gass, William. Culp, 1985. (Box 50)
    - Material relating to illustration, some typography
    - Unbound sheets
  - Material relating to D'Offay stationery; miscellaneous photographs, illustration material; ms. text of poem from Gregory Corso, The Day After Humankind. Grenfell Press Publications. Duncan, Robert. A Paris Visit, 1985. (Box 51)
  - Material relating to illustration Burroughs, William. The Cat Inside. 1986.
  - Original artwork (possibly not for Cat Inside) Morrow, Bradford. A Bestiary. 1990.
  - Miscellaneous unbound sheets 6-8. Proofs of preliminary matter
  - Whale (Box 52)
  - Lemming
  - Horse
  - Little Cock
  - Cheetah
  - Mongoose
  - Giraffe (Box 53)
  - Yak
  - Grouse
  - Miscellaneous proofs. Burroughs, William. The Cat Inside. 1986.
  - Material relating to illustration Miscellaneous Publications. Michaux, Henri. Ideograms in China, 1984.
  - Material relating to illustration
  - Grenfell Press Publications Duncan, Robert. A Paris Visit. 1985. (Box 54)
    - Material relating to illustration two broadsheets, (one dated December, 1979 and the other undated), showing the press's typeface